# MARIA DOBROVOLSKYA

MARKETING GRAPHIC DESIGNER

#### **DETAILS**

#### PHONE

058 5851762

#### FΜΔΙΙ

dobrovolskayamaria@gmail.com

#### **LINKS**

My Portfolio

Dribble

#### **SKILLS**



Adobe Illustrator



Adobe Photoshop



Adobe Indesign



Adobe XD



Figma



Affinity Designer



Procreate



Microsoft PowerPoint



Microsoft Excel



Microsoft Word

## **LANGUAGES**

Hebrew High Level
English High Level
Russian Native

## **PROFILE**

I am an experienced graphic designer with a track record of creating successful **print** and **digital** projects from conception to completion. With strong attention to detail and a client-focused approach, I am skilled in both independent and teamoriented work

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Marketing Graphic Designer, Chekmarx**

2022 - Present

Checkmarx is a global software security company

- Developing campaign materials and producing assets: presentations, data visualization, newsletters, banners, web pages, social media campaigns, events, eBooks, one-pagers, infographics, presentations, internal communication, brochures, rollups, customer portal, email templates and blogs
- Collaborating with multidisciplinary product and marketing teams and managing multiple projects at once

## Web Graphic Designer & Illustrator, Freelance

2020 - 2022

- · Web: Design of homepage, landing pages, product and solution pages.
- Images, infographics, and illustrations for digital, interactive, and print design fields, company logos, and websites
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$  Branding, company gifts, presentations, brochures
- · Collateral: eBooks, one-pagers, case studies, infographics
- · Social media: Tiles, banners

## **Graphic Creative Designer, Maskit**

2018 - 2020

Maskit is the first and only israeli fashion house established in 1954

 Designed collections from sketches to the final product, hand-painting on textile, making sketches for embroidery. Created and Illustrated creative concepts in a wide range of graphics and layouts for product illustrations

## Creative Designer, Katya Dobryakova Ltd

2018 - 2020

Katya Dobryakova is a Russian high-end contemporary fashion brand

- · Created graphic and textile concepts, embroidery design and art-management
- Over 5 years of work, 10 collections of exclusive clothes have been successfully released under my supervision product development process

## **EDUCATION**

## Master Of Arts(MA) At Moscow State Textile University

2006 -2011

Stilyst textile designer, creating designs and prints for woven, printed, and knitted items in the textile industry